(Howard:)You have any idea
what you're getting
(Howard:)Sheldon for his birthday?
(Raj:)He's been fascinated
with dinosaurs lately.
(Raj:)Maybe we could get him a fossil.
(Leonard:)Well, just don't
get anything Jurassic.
(Leonard:)He feels like that whole chunk
of time has gone Hollywood.
(Leonard:)Hey, uh, you know,
(Leonard:)he told a sad story
about how his sister
(Leonard:)tricked him into thinking Batman
was coming to his party.
(Howard:)That's funny.
(Howard:)Let's do that.
(Leonard:)Maybe we could get Batman
to actually show up.
(Raj:)You mean, some guy
in a lame suit?
(Leonard:)Or a real Batman.
Hey, Stuart?
(Leonard:)Didn't you try to get Adam West
to do a signing here once?
(Stuart:)Yeah, but there was kind of
a scheduling conflict.
(Stuart:)He, uh, wanted to know
when he'd get paid.
(Stuart:)And I wouldn't tell him.
(Leonard:)Can I get his contact info?
(Stuart:)Sure, uh, but
just so you know,
(Stuart:)he's kind of a diva.
(Leonard:)He is?
Oh, yeah.
(Stuart:)Won't take the bus.
(Stuart:)He won't pack his own lunch.
(Stuart:)Won't let you spend
the night on his couch.